{
    "subject": "resource/Bruce_Willis",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/West_Germany",
    "human_readable": "Bruce Willis was born in West Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9734138250350952,
            "question": "Did Bruce Willis grow up in West Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9311881065368652,
            "question": "In what region of Germany was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459752202033997,
            "question": "What country was Bruce Willis born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8444451093673706,
            "question": "Where was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103258967399597,
            "question": "When was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6195100545883179,
            "question": "What nationality is Bruce Willis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43683376908302307,
            "question": "Is Bruce Willis American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41311681270599365,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2513495683670044,
            "question": "Has Bruce Willis ever lived in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1651747226715088,
            "question": "What are some of Bruce Willis's famous roles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bruce Willis was born in West Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7833_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Bruce Willis ever lived in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7833_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bruce Willis known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7833_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bruce Willis American?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7833_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7833_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Bruce Willis was born in West Germany\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Bruce Willis was born on March 19, 1955, in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany, but only one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7833/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt) mentions \"born on March 19, 1955\" and another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7833/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt) mentions \"Born Mar 19, 1955 in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany\". However, the other documents also mention that he is American and this information contradicts with the fact that only one document says \"West Germany\" and another doesn't say where he was born."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Bruce Willis was born on March 19, 1955, in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany. Therefore, the statement \"Bruce Willis was born in West Germany\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the overwhelming majority of sources (5 out of 6) consistently mention Bruce Willis' birthplace as Idar-Oberstein, West Germany on March 19, 1955.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}